Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection, 1866-2007
RG.028
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
9.0 Cubic feet 9 boxes
This collection contains images of Poly faculty, students, alumni, visiting lecturers, and other associated professionals spanning from 1866 to 2007
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research without restrictions.
Biographical/Historical note
The images in this collection were transferred to the archives from various departments over a number of years. Some of these departments included: Alumni Relations, Development, Student Activities, Public Relations, and the President's Office. The exact provenance of the loosely organized photographs was unknown.
During processing in 2014, most of the photographs were re-housed and additional information about the subject was added to the file when possible.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged alphabetically, by last name. A miscellaneous series of unidentified portraits follows the alphabetical series.
Scope and Contents note
The Poly Archives Portrait Collection contains images of Poly faculty, students, alumni, visiting lecturers, and other associated professionals spanning from 1866 to 2007. Many of the early images in the collection are photocopies rather than original photographs.
Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn.; Polytechnic Institute of New York.; Polytechnic Institute of NYU.; Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.).
- A
  - Abbinanti, Andrew P, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aber, Janice E., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abrahams, Robert A., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abritz, Santos, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acker, Joseph G., undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ackenberg, Robert, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Eleanor, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adler, Benjamin, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adorno, Candy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agarwal, Jagdish, [1977] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Agosta, Vito, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aitlamison, Shelley, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alaimo, Salvatore J., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - “Odd Albert”, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Albert, S. G., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alfrey, Turner, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alpert, Seymour, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Alstadt, Don M., undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alvarez, Ernest, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ambrosino, Michael A., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Anderson, Dorna, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Andrews, Audrey, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Andrews, John W., undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Angelery, Henry W., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anlinker, Max, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Armand, Fritz, 1993, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Arnold, Stephen, 1979, 1982, 1994, 1998, 2004, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arnov, Boris, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aschkenasy, Herbert, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Assmus, Alexi, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Atkinson, Fred, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Atlas, Sheldon, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Auburn, Norman P., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Azarencov, Vladimir, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- B
  - Bachman, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Backhas, John G., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Baclini, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bain, Jonathan, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Baker, William, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Balaban, Philip, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Baldwin, G., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Balfour, Menachem, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Balriki [?], 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Balsara, Nitash P., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Banks, Ephraim, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Baranello, Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Barclay, General John A., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Barnickle, Rose Marie, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Baron, Thelma, circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Barone, Stephan, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Barrett, Gilbert C., undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Barron, Edward T., 1998, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bartlett, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bartlett, Ford, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Bashe, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Bassett, Preston R., undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bassett, Robert J., undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bassin, Milton G., undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Battelle, Richard A. Nathan, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Battend, A., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Battler, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Baum, Eleanor, circa 1997 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Baumgartel, Robert G., undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Beardsley, Seymour W., undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Becker, Neal Dow, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Beckett, Cedric D., undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Beckmann, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Bellin, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bellomo-Erisco, Anthony, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bender, Barbara, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Benenati, Robert F., undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bentson, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Benvenuto, Harry, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Berg, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Berge, G. Stanley, circa 1999 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Berger, Mark, 1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Berger, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bergman, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bergstein, S., undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Beringer, F. Marshall, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Berkman, Lillian, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Berkovits, Barouh V., undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Berkowitz, Leonard, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Berson, Yair, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Bertoni, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Bienenstock, Arthur, 1957, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Billy, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bishoff, Willard, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Blair, Joline, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Blecher, Franklin H., 1977, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Blecherman, Barry, undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Blesser, William (Bill), undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Bloch, Erich, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Bloom, Barry M., undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Bloom, Martin, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Boes, Warren N., 1958, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Boesch, Francis (Frank) T., undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Boley, Bruno A., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Bolicki, undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bolle, Donald, 1995, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Bongiorno, Joseph J., undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Bonvillian, E. Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Boorstyn, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Boukli-Hacene, Mokhtar, undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Brabson, Rodney M., undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Braga, Giola M., undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Brand, F.A., undated; w (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Brand, Robert G., undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Brandenstein, Albert, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Branscomb, Lewis M., undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Braun, Ludwig, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Braun, Norman, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Braverman, Lisa, circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Bregman, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Brenman, Jerold E., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Brenner, F. Cecil, undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Bresler, Sidney A., undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Bressler, Richard J., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Brierly, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Brigandi, Anthony J., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Brigandi, Celest, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Brockway, Albert L., undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Bronnimann, Herve, undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Brous, Bernard, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Brown, Joseph D., undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Brown, Robert G., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Brown, Robert P., undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Brown, Ron, undated (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Brownman, Harold L., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Bruins, Paul F., undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Bruns, George H. Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Bruno, Joseph, circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Bueche, Arthur, undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Bugliarello, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Bulkin, Bernard J., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Bumas, Lester O., undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Burns, Ursula M., undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Buschman, Wilbur J., undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
- C
  - Cacciatore, Sebastian, circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cadoff, Irving B., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cahill, [Dan], undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cahill, Patrick, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Calarco, Vincent A., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Caldwell, Benjamin Palmer, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Caldwell, Winston F. Lt. Col., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Calviello, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Camarda, Charles J., undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Campanili, Sal, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Campbell, George Jr., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cammarata, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Canziam, V., undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Canzilli, Edmund J., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Capuro, Albert D., 1954, 1955, 1959, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Caramore, Chris, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Carassa, Francesco, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Carbonell, Robert J., undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cardenas, R., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Carey, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Carey, Bob, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Carlino, Joe, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Carpenter, Scott, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Carroll, Pat, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Casamassima, Salvatore, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Casazzone, Ralph W., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Casey, William J., undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cassara, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cassedy, Edward S., undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Castleman, Louis, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Catacosinos, W.J., undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Catherine, Joseph W., undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cevasco, Francis M., undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chaikin, Phil, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Chance, Britton, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Chang, David C., 1993, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Chang, Ifay, 1996, 1997, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Chang, Morris, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Chang, Sooyang, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chang, Chun-Yen, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Chao, Jonathan H., undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chen, Wen Xiong, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cheng, Benjamin K., 1997, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cheng, Shuming, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Chesla, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Chiang, Yi-Jen, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chin, Paul, circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chittenden, Jonathan Brace, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Chodash, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Choe, Wolhee, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Choudhury, Deo, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Christodoulou, Symeon, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Chu, J.C., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Chudnovsky Brothers (David and Gregory), undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Chung, KunMo, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Church, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Philip R., undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Clothier, Robert Clarkson (1885-1970), undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Cochran, David H., undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Codrington, Yolanda, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Coffin, L.W., undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cohen, Abby Joseph, circa 1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Cohn, Arthur, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Cok, Amy, crica 1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Collins, Edward E., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Collins, Frank C., undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Collins, George Stuart (1862-1935), undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Coner, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Conigliaro, S.A., undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Coniglione, Joseph, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Conklin, David A., undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Conoscenti, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Conti, James J., undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Cooper, Maggie Townsend, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Copley, Al., undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Corey, Michael R., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Cornick, Jonathan, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Correale, William H., undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Cortina, Thomas J., undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Corwin, Bernard (also listed as Cohen), undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Cosentino, Louis C., circa 1980 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Cowman, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Cox, Donald M., undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Crawford, Frederick L., undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Crotty, Paul A., undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Crowley, K., undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Crump, Jesse, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Cuomo, Mario, undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Curington, Calvin Capt., undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Czarkowski, Dariusz, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - C Negatives- Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
- D
  - Daly, Tom, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Dalziel, Robert, 1979, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Damadian, Raymond, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - D'Amato Anthony S., circa 1998 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - D'Antonio, Carmine, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Daniels, M, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Daruvala, Homi S., undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Das, Nirod, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Davenport, John L., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - David, Edward E., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Davis, Alan R., undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Davis, H.L., undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Debroy, Partha, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - DeCicco, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - DeGaeta, Albert M., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - DeGaeta, Edythe, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - DeGarta, Albert, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Delis, Alex, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Denmark, Ellis, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - DePalma, Amy, circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Deutsch, Emeric, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Deutsch, Dr. Sid, undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Develet, Jean A. Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Devlin, Robert H., undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - DeVries, Duane, undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - DeWitt, Henry Ginnel, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - DiBartolo, S. John, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Dibner, A. Bern (1897-1988), 1921, 1950, 1951, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Dibner, David, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Diemer, Ferdinand P., undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Diestel, James E. pfc., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - DiLeo, Christopher C., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - DiNardo, Anthony, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Djerassi, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Dobkin, James C., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Dodd, L., undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Dolins, Francine, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Donahue, Thomas L., 1945, 1952, 1954, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Dorzback, Irene, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Doty, Paul, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Doucette, David R., undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Draper, Charles Stark (1901-1987), undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Droge, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Dropkin, Dr. John J., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Drori, Ze'er, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Duba, John G., undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Dubanowitz, Paul M., undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Dubos, Rene, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Dufner, Donna, undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Duke, Gus George, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Durborow, undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Duryea, Samuel, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
- E
  - Eaton, George S., 1952, 1954, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Eckert, Norman C., undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Eden, Dick, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Edwards, Alph, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Egan, James W. Jr., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Eirich, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Eirich, Frederick R. (1905-2005), 1958, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Eisele, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Eisenberg, Ann, 1985, 1986, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - El-Batal, Randa, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Elion, Gertrude, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ellerstein, Stuart, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Elliott, Edward H., undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ellner, George, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Emma, Rose, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Engeler, W.E., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Epstein, Jerome, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Erickson, Burt, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Erickson, Ernst S., Jr., undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Erkip, Elza, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Esrig, Melvin I., circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Everetts, John Jr., circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ewald, Paul P., 1954, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Exelbert, Myron A., 1956 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- F
  - Falcocchio, John C., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Falcon, Joseph A., circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fankuchen, Isidor, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Farmer, Phillip W., undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Farrell, Bob, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fay, Irving Wetherbee (1861-1936), undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Feddersen, Ronald E., undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Feintuch, Howard M., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Felson, Leopold B., undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Feroli, Theresa, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ferri, Antonio, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fialkov, Herman, 1982, 1985, 1986, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Field, Frank, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Figaro, Billy, circa 2005 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Filosa, Angelo, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Finestone, Arnold B., undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Fink, J.H., undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Finkelstein, Stanley, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Fisanick, Georgia, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Fischer, George, 1978, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Fishler, Leslie S., undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Fitzpatrick, Jim, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Flaster, Gerald A., undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Flory, Paul John, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Flynn, Robert J. "Bob", undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Focke, H.H., circa 1990 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Folan, Lorcan M., undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Ford, Frank J., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Foster, Ronald, 1954, 1955, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Fox, Beauvais, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Fox, Jerome, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Foxen, Richard William, 1997, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Fraim, P.B., undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Frankl, Phyllis, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Freimark, Steve, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Friedman, Leonard J., 2000 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Friedman, Rachelle, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Frieman, Edward A., 1986, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Friend, William "Bill", 1985, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Frisch, Ivan, 1983, 1986, 1992, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Fritz, Brother Raymond L., 1977, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Frolich, Gerhard J., undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Fromm, Winfield E., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Frothingham, Isaac H., late 1880s (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fruendlich, J., undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fung, Haang, circa 1984 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Furnas, C.C., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- G
  - Gaines, W., undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Galil, Uzia, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Galina, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Gallagher, Evan, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Gallagher, Jean, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Galloway, E.C., undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Garbe, Edward, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Garcia, Jose, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Garetz, Bruce A., undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Garofalo, Frank, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Garwin, Richard L., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Gavin, Joseph G., undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Gaylor, Walter, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Gellis, Roberta, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Gendel, Michael, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Genovese, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Georgakis, Christos, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Georgi, Gunter, undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Gerhardt, Kenneth C., undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Gersten, Marvin C., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Gertler, Janos, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Geva, Eran, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Ghandehari, Masoud, undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Giacobello, Bartholemew F., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Giba, John, 1966, 1993, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Gilbert, Jack, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Gilbert, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Gillett, Elizabeth R.H., undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Gillette, David, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gilmont, Roger, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Giordano, Anthony B. (and wife Peggy), circa 1950, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Glenn, Alvin B., undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Gluckman, Joshua, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Gobran, Riad, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Gold, Albert, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Gold, Bernard, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Gold, Lawrence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Gold, Louis, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Goldberg, Samuel David, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Golden, William T., undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Goldin, Daniel S., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Goldman, David S., undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Goldman, Irwin, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Goldman, Jack, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Goldmark, Peter C., undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Goldsmith, Clifford Henry, 1996, 1998, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Goldstein, Harvey, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Goldstein, Matthew, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Goodman, David J., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Goodman, Murray, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Gordon, Emmet F., undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Gordon, Jayne, circa 1996 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Gould, Gordon, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Grad, Arthur, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Granato, Richardson, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Granis, Michael, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Grantz, Howard E., undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Grau, Herman, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Gray, Lucille R., undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Gray, Nomer, undated; 9 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Grayson, Laurence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Greco, William J., undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Green, Mark, 1994, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Greene, Barry (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Greenfield, S. Steve, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Greenshields, Bruce D., undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Greenwood, Doug, undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Gregor, Harry, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Grieco, Linda, undated (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Griemsmann, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Griffis, Fletcher H. "Bud", 1999, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Grill, Jeanette, undated (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Gross, Richard A., 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gross, S.H., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Grossman, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Grossman, Fred, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gruber, Helmut, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gruehr, Anatole R., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Guerrieri, Anne, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gugick, Leonard, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guglielmi, Marco, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gupta, Sunil, circa 1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- H
  - Haas, Zygmunt, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Habach, George F., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Haddad, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hadimioglu, H., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hague, Bernard, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hall, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hallingby, Paul Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Halpern, Gregory, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hammoud, Harry P., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hampden, Walter, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Han, Chang Dae "Paul", 1974, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hancock, Herbie, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hanson, Jimmy, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hao, Xiaolong, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Harazim, William, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Harker, David (1906-1991), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Harris, Wanda, circa 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Harrison, Gen, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Harrington, Paul R., undated (Box 4, Folder 29)